Report!
Spies report that General Song has returned to the capital.
Only by faking illness can we lure the enemy in.
Your Majesty.
What did I do wrong?
Why are you treating me like this?
Get out! Get out of here!
If you make another sound, I'll kill you.
Your Majesty, I know I was wrong.
Please spare my life.
Please!
Get out!
I told you to get out!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please don't send me away.
Make another sound, and I will kill you.
Has His Majesty become a tyrant again?
Should we leave?
Did we overact?
What do you know?
This is the only way the Grand Princess will believe
that you haven't fully recovered from the Gu poison.
If you don't destroy the root,
the problem will just return.
Your Majesty,
let go of my hand.
I can't breathe.
Your Majesty.
I know I was wrong.
A bunch of useless fools.
Do you all look down on me?
Your Majesty, what's wrong, Your Majesty?
Summon the imperial physician. Imperial physician!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty, what's wrong?
Imperial physician, hurry!
Since a few days ago,
His Majesty's temper has become increasingly violent.
Now he even tries to kill Cangyue,
his favorite.
He then fainted from exhaustion and rage.
I'm afraid his days are numbered.
Step down.
Yes.
The poison acted up two days earlier than expected.
The mother Gu is overbearing,
and the child Gu is not to be underestimated.
You can rest assured, Your Highness.
I really didn't expect
your Gu-refining skills to be so exquisite.
Of course.
Your Highness, General Song has arrived.
I pay my respects to Your Highness.
Please rise, General Song.
Master Fan said in his message that time is urgent.
We must take action while the Emperor is ill.
So I took the liberty of bringing the military seal to see Your Highness.
I knew I wasn't wrong about you.
I wish Your Highness a triumphant return.
Your Majesty is destined by heaven.
I wish Your Majesty a triumphant return.
Could you pretend to be sick a bit more convincingly?
I am the Emperor.
I can do whatever I want.
By the way.
They will make their move tonight.
What if the Grand Princess has a backup plan?
What?
Are you addicted to pretending to be sick?
There is no one else here.
It was your idea.
Now you are taking it more seriously than I am.
Didn't you say everything is ready
except for the final piece?
Give me your hand.
Keep this token safe.
If anything goes wrong,
someone will escort you out of the palace.
We've been together for so long.
At the most critical moment,
you can't just kick me out.
Xuan.
Cen Zhoujin.
Jin Cen Zhoujin.
Ning Feihai.
Liang Shuang Xiyong.
Liang Quan Huiyong.
Lan.
Xuli.
Xu Li.
Fan.